Does every love story have the same old
clichéd boy meets girl story
or has Chennai Love Story
played a new mind game in the name of romance? If
you are thinking that it will be a cold romcom film
then you might be wrong brother, so brother
let us know what the reality is, so friends,
everything is great, my name is Neeraj and I watched
Chennai Love Story, if you like the video then do
hype it by liking it, so brother, the
story of this film revolves around a Navy woman who
runs away from a heavy emotional trauma of her past and
comes to Chennai.  Now here Bandi
meets a boy named Steven
who is a struggling guy with a never give up
attitude.  Now here a
broken girl whose heart is broken and a
guy with big dreams, when these two
meet each other, then brother life gives them a
new chance.  So will there be a new
heartbreak now?  So this story is
not about love but
it also
explains [music] how to deal with one's past and trauma.  Now brother, the twists in the film
come where you would
not expect.  Now let's review this film.
What's special and what's rubbish.   Whether
this 28 hour film deserves time
or not.  First of all, if we talk about the performance,
both the actors have done a great
job here.  On one hand, he has a
dream of becoming a frustrated director, so
whatever work the guy has done seems absolutely natural.   On
the other hand, Shri Gauri has also done a great job.
Brother, the prisoner is in a lot of trauma
and when the prisoner speaks the dialogue, brother,
you also start feeling pity for her.  The
visuals and cinematography of the film are quite good.  The
location of Chennai has been shown very well.  In
other words, the
warm tone of the film looks quite good.  Brother, the
BGM of this film is the life of this film.
Talking about hidden details, Steven as a
struggling director, there are
many such people roaming around in Chennai brother.